<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vuejs on Bachdx&#39;s</title>
    <link>https://bachdx2812.github.io/tags/vuejs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vuejs on Bachdx&#39;s</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bachdx2812.github.io/tags/vuejs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan Vue Festival 2018</title>
      <link>https://bachdx2812.github.io/posts/vue-fes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bachdx2812.github.io/posts/vue-fes/</guid>
      <description>It has been an honor and pleasure meeting and talking with Evan You - the creator of VueJS
And I had a picture with him. Great Anyway, in Evan speach, he said that Vue 3.0 will be faster, smaller and easier to maitain. Really looking forward to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The making of My Personal Support Bot</title>
      <link>https://bachdx2812.github.io/posts/zalo-auto-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bachdx2812.github.io/posts/zalo-auto-chat/</guid>
      <description>Its 3am and I really feel sleepy right now.
Purpose I&amp;rsquo;ve been always impressed by J.A.R.V.I.S in Iron Man movies. But please dont get me wrong. Currently Im not good enough to build such an intelligent bot like that. I just want a simple bot which do some simple daily tasks for me. Because its gonna be fun isnt it?
The first function(2018-10-27) The purpose Im currently working far from my family (Im in Japan and my family back in VietNam).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The making of Todo App using Vuex</title>
      <link>https://bachdx2812.github.io/posts/todo-vuex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 21:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bachdx2812.github.io/posts/todo-vuex/</guid>
      <description>Its has been a while since my first post I&amp;rsquo;ve to commit that Im kinda lazy lately
Okay..Enough trash talk So I&amp;rsquo;ve bee working with VueJs for a while which is very cool. But the more I work with VueJs, the more I realize that I need a &amp;ldquo;state management system&amp;rdquo; cause everytime I break down the components and add actions into them&amp;hellip;It become really messy
So I decided to learn VueX</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Fun &#39;project&#39;</title>
      <link>https://bachdx2812.github.io/posts/image-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 15:53:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bachdx2812.github.io/posts/image-fun/</guid>
      <description>This is my first ever post on my blog So I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on some of my pet projects for the last few days in my 3-holiday(三連休) which is deployed at ImageFun with VueJS
Here come some screenshots
HomePage Image filter The idea I have absolutely no idea about what I tried to build (lol) . Just fell so boring and wanna do some interesting stuff so I do this for fun actually.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>